herald-dispatch.com 2006-12-05

# herald-dispatch.com Privacy Policy <span class="story_bodycopy"> <p>The following Privacy Policy governs herald-dispatch.com’s online information collection practices. Specifically, it outlines the types of information that herald-dispatch.com gathers about you while you are using the herald-dispatch.com website (the “Service”), and the ways in which herald-dispatch.com uses this information. This Privacy Policy, including our children’s privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means (for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail). <p> Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting the herald-dispatch.com website, you agree that your use of our Service, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy and our <A href="http://www.herald-dispatch.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/99999999/NEWS01/50812001">Terms of Service</A>. Because the Web is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we'll post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this website and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the herald-dispatch.com website after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified. <p> <b>Your California Privacy Rights</b> <p> California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to: <p> Online Privacy Coordinator<br> Newspaper Division<br> 7950 Jones Branch Drive<br> McLean, VA 22107<br> <p> <b>How We Collect and Use Information</b> <p> We may collect and store personal or other information that you voluntarily supply to us online while using the Service (e.g., while on the herald-dispatch.com site or in responding via email to a feature provided on the herald-dispatch.com site). <p> We also collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate online through the Service. For example, we may collect information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic on the herald-dispatch.com site. We also may use a standard feature found in browser software called a "cookie” to enhance your experience on the herald-dispatch.com website. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use the herald-dispatch.com, cookies help us deliver advertisements, identify how many unique browsers visit us, and track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the herald-dispatch.com site where you may have entered preference information before. herald-dispatch.com also may use web beacons (also known as “transparent GIFs”) to access cookies and to count users who visit the herald-dispatch.com site or open herald-dispatch.com’s HTML-formatted email messages. <p> herald-dispatch.com uses the information it collects from you while you are using the Service in a variety of ways, including using the information to customize features and advertising that appear on the Service. We also may provide your information to third parties, such as service providers, contractors, and advertisers, for a variety of purposes. Unless you inform us otherwise, herald-dispatch.com reserves the right to use, and to disclose to third parties, all of the information collected from and about you while you are using the Service in any way and for any purpose, such as to enable herald-dispatch.com or a third party to provide you with information about products and services. If you do not wish your information to be used for these purposes, you must send a letter to the Online Privacy Coordinator whose address is listed at the end of this Privacy Policy requesting to be taken off any lists of information that may be used for these purposes or that may be given or sold to third-party vendors. <p> Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties online – for example on message boards, web logs, through email, or in chat areas – that information can be seen, collected and used by others besides herald-dispatch.com. herald-dispatch.com cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information. <p> Some of our third-party advertisers and ad servers that place and present advertising on the Service also may collect information from you via cookies, web beacons or similar technologies. These third-party advertisers and ad servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness, or for other purposes. The use and collection of your information by these third-party advertisers and ad servers is governed by the relevant third-party’s privacy policy and is not covered by our Privacy Policy. Indeed, the privacy policies of these third-party advertisers and ad servers may be different from ours. If you have any concerns about a third party’s use of cookies or use of your information, you should visit that party’s website and review its privacy policy. <p> herald-dispatch.com also includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third-party products or services through the Service, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services. <p> We also make some content, products and services available through our Service through cooperative relationships with third-party providers, where the brands of our provider partner appear on the Service in connection with such content, products and/or services. We may share with our provider partner any information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in cooperation with our provider partner. In some cases, the provider partner may collect information from you directly, in which cases the privacy policy of our provider partner may apply to the provider partner’s use of your information. The privacy policy of our provider partners may differ from ours. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners, you should contact the provider partner directly for more information. <p> We are an affiliate of the CareerBuilder online careers service. Through our cooperative relationship with CareerBuilder, we are able to provide you with access to the CareerBuilder products and services through a co-branded CareerBuilder site. When you provide information through the co-branded CareerBuilder site, CareerBuilder may share your information with us and we may use the information consistent with this Privacy Policy. <p> Likewise, we are an affiliate of the Topix.net online news service, which enables us to provide you with access to Topix.net products and services through a co-branded Topix.net site. When you provide information through the co-branded Topix.net site, Topix.net may share your information with us and we may use that information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. <p> Be aware that we may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our <A href="http://www.herald-dispatch.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/99999999/NEWS01/50812001">Terms of Service</A> agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of our Services, the public, or herald-dispatch.com. <p> Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we, some or all of our assets, or one or more of our websites is acquired by another company, information about our users may be among the transferred assets. <p> <b>Children’s Privacy Statement</b> <p> This children’s privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, and provides important information regarding your rights under federal law with respect to such information. <p> • This Service is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service. We screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of thirteen from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service. • Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we also do NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties. • We do NOT knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Service. • Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we do NOT condition the participation in the Service’s online activities of a child under thirteen on providing personally identifiable information. <p> <b>How To Make Changes to Your Information</b> <p> If you have subscribed to one or more herald-dispatch.com email newsletters, you may change your subscriber information, modify your subscriptions, and/or unsubscribe from these newsletters at any time by visiting [insert URL]. <p> <b>Questions Regarding Privacy</b> <p> If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of herald-dispatch.com, or your dealings with herald-dispatch.com, you can contact: <p> Lynne Marsh,<br> 946 Fifth Avenue<br> Huntington, W.V. 25701</p> </span>

The following Privacy Policy governs herald-dispatch.com’s online information collection practices. Specifically, it outlines the types of information that herald-dispatch.com gathers about you while you are using the herald-dispatch.com website (the “Service”), and the ways in which herald-dispatch.com uses this information. This Privacy Policy, including our children’s privacy statement, does not apply to any information you may provide to us or that we may collect offline and/or through other means (for example, at a live event, via telephone, or through the mail). 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. By visiting the herald-dispatch.com website, you agree that your use of our Service, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Privacy Policy and our [Terms of Service](http://www.herald-dispatch.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/99999999/NEWS01/50812001). Because the Web is an evolving medium, we may need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, in which case we'll post the changes to this Privacy Policy on this website and update the Effective Date of the policy to reflect the date of the changes. By continuing to use the herald-dispatch.com website after we post any such changes, you accept the Privacy Policy as modified. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to: 

Online Privacy Coordinator  
Newspaper Division  
7950 Jones Branch Drive  
McLean, VA 22107  

**How We Collect and Use Information**

We may collect and store personal or other information that you voluntarily supply to us online while using the Service (e.g., while on the herald-dispatch.com site or in responding via email to a feature provided on the herald-dispatch.com site). 

We also collect and store information that is generated automatically as you navigate online through the Service. For example, we may collect information about your computer's connection to the Internet, which allows us, among other things, to improve the delivery of our web pages to you and to measure traffic on the herald-dispatch.com site. We also may use a standard feature found in browser software called a "cookie” to enhance your experience on the herald-dispatch.com website. Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your hard drive for record-keeping purposes. By showing how and when visitors use the herald-dispatch.com, cookies help us deliver advertisements, identify how many unique browsers visit us, and track user trends and patterns. They also prevent you from having to re-enter your preferences on certain areas of the herald-dispatch.com site where you may have entered preference information before. herald-dispatch.com also may use web beacons (also known as “transparent GIFs”) to access cookies and to count users who visit the herald-dispatch.com site or open herald-dispatch.com’s HTML-formatted email messages. 

herald-dispatch.com uses the information it collects from you while you are using the Service in a variety of ways, including using the information to customize features and advertising that appear on the Service. We also may provide your information to third parties, such as service providers, contractors, and advertisers, for a variety of purposes. Unless you inform us otherwise, herald-dispatch.com reserves the right to use, and to disclose to third parties, all of the information collected from and about you while you are using the Service in any way and for any purpose, such as to enable herald-dispatch.com or a third party to provide you with information about products and services. If you do not wish your information to be used for these purposes, you must send a letter to the Online Privacy Coordinator whose address is listed at the end of this Privacy Policy requesting to be taken off any lists of information that may be used for these purposes or that may be given or sold to third-party vendors. 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily make your personal information available for viewing by third parties online – for example on message boards, web logs, through email, or in chat areas – that information can be seen, collected and used by others besides herald-dispatch.com. herald-dispatch.com cannot be responsible for any unauthorized third-party use of such information. 

Some of our third-party advertisers and ad servers that place and present advertising on the Service also may collect information from you via cookies, web beacons or similar technologies. These third-party advertisers and ad servers may use the information they collect to help present their advertisements, to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness, or for other purposes. The use and collection of your information by these third-party advertisers and ad servers is governed by the relevant third-party’s privacy policy and is not covered by our Privacy Policy. Indeed, the privacy policies of these third-party advertisers and ad servers may be different from ours. If you have any concerns about a third party’s use of cookies or use of your information, you should visit that party’s website and review its privacy policy. 

herald-dispatch.com also includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. When you access another website or purchase third-party products or services through the Service, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you are visiting or the provider of such products or services. 

We also make some content, products and services available through our Service through cooperative relationships with third-party providers, where the brands of our provider partner appear on the Service in connection with such content, products and/or services. We may share with our provider partner any information you provide, or that is collected, in the course of visiting any pages that are made available in cooperation with our provider partner. In some cases, the provider partner may collect information from you directly, in which cases the privacy policy of our provider partner may apply to the provider partner’s use of your information. The privacy policy of our provider partners may differ from ours. If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of one of our provider partners, you should contact the provider partner directly for more information. 

We are an affiliate of the CareerBuilder online careers service. Through our cooperative relationship with CareerBuilder, we are able to provide you with access to the CareerBuilder products and services through a co-branded CareerBuilder site. When you provide information through the co-branded CareerBuilder site, CareerBuilder may share your information with us and we may use the information consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

Likewise, we are an affiliate of the Topix.net online news service, which enables us to provide you with access to Topix.net products and services through a co-branded Topix.net site. When you provide information through the co-branded Topix.net site, Topix.net may share your information with us and we may use that information in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

Be aware that we may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our [Terms of Service](http://www.herald-dispatch.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/99999999/NEWS01/50812001) agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of users of our Services, the public, or herald-dispatch.com. 

Please also note that as our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that we, some or all of our assets, or one or more of our websites is acquired by another company, information about our users may be among the transferred assets. 

**Children’s Privacy Statement**

This children’s privacy statement explains our practices with respect to the online collection and use of personal information from children under the age of thirteen, and provides important information regarding your rights under federal law with respect to such information. 

• This Service is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do NOT knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service. We screen users who wish to provide personal information in order to prevent users under the age of thirteen from providing such information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from a user under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service. • Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we also do NOT knowingly distribute such information to third parties. • We do NOT knowingly allow children under the age of thirteen to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through the Service. • Because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen as part of the Service, we do NOT condition the participation in the Service’s online activities of a child under thirteen on providing personally identifiable information. 

**How To Make Changes to Your Information**

If you have subscribed to one or more herald-dispatch.com email newsletters, you may change your subscriber information, modify your subscriptions, and/or unsubscribe from these newsletters at any time by visiting [insert URL]. 

**Questions Regarding Privacy**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the privacy practices of herald-dispatch.com, or your dealings with herald-dispatch.com, you can contact: 

Lynne Marsh,  
946 Fifth Avenue  
Huntington, W.V. 25701
